

TypeScript, Angular, SaSS, NGRX

# OPROFILE

Developer with two years of experiences in Web development.

Passionate about creating and understanding the dynamics of the technology market, Master in Business Digital Strategy.

I am looking for a place where I can combine my programming skills with my experience from the social sciences to improve the products that the client receives.

### CONTACT

**Phone** +55 (12) 936180526

**Email** radapls8@gmail.com

Website https://radapls.github.io

in LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/radapls

• Location São José dos Campos or Remote

## LANGUAGES

Spanish - **Native**English - **Intermediate**Portuguese - **Intermediate** 

#### HOBBIES

Cooking Sewing AR filters

# TOOLS

Intermediate professional competence









Intermediate professional competence









# **EXPERIENCE**

### January 2021 - Present

Frontend Developer, Wiboo Company

Creation of functionalities, maintenance of the state of the web and mobile code.

Management of Planner under the Scrum Agile model for the follow-up of tasks and deliverables. **Development tools:** TypeScript / NativeScript, Angular, Saas, NGRX, HTTP requests.

## July 2020- December 2021

Social Researcher, Instituto de Estudios Interculturales

March 2019 - December 2019

**Devlovery Unit Member,** Secretaria de Gobierno, Alcaldia Municipal de Santiago de Cali. ■

January - June 2018

Research Assistant, Misión de Observación Electoral

March - June 2017

**Research Instructor**, Carrera de Ciencia Política, Pontificia Universidad Javeriana Cali. ■

August - November 2016

Research Instructor, Instituto de Estudios Interculturales

### EDUCATION

2021-2022

**Universidad ICESI -** Master in Digital Business Strategy Emphasis on prototyping and user validation on the different projects. Creation of the SIGET-RB for the management of Telepacfico transportation.

2014-2019

**Pontificia Universidad Javeriana Cali -** Political Scientist Creation of two research seedbeds. Development of design skills.